momlessmom.com 2018-08-24

# Privacy Policy - MomLess Mom

_Here at MomLess Mom,   we are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement._

## **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

1\.  To personalize your experience – your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

 2\.  To improve our website -we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we  receive from you

3\. To improve customer service – your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs 

 4\. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

We require information outlined above to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

### **We may use the information to improve our products and services.**

If you have signed up for our newsletter, we may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. We will never sell your information.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

##   **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

 We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

##   **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

##   **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

##   **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

You may choose not to supply any personal information. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at amomlessmom@gmail.com and we will delete your record upon request.

By using our site, you consent to our website Privacy Policy. 

## **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on April 23, 2018

##  

## **Contacting Us**   

 If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may use the Contact form on this blog.
